NIKI FEREIDOONI

Toronto, ON M5T1Y2

Phone: 416-735-6928 | Email: nikifereidooni@gmail.com LinkedIn: ca.linkedin.com/in/nfereidooni/ | GitHub: github.com/nfereidooni/ Portfolio: nfereidooni.github.io/nf-react-portfolio/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer leveraging graphic arts & technical background to build beautifully designed websites. Recently earned a certificate in full stack web development from the University of Toronto, with newly developed skills in Javascript, CSS, Node.js, React.js and mySQL. Also earned a BTech in Graphic Communications Management in 2014. Motivated to find ways to make things BETTER - more efficient, responsive, engaging, and beautiful. I am highly organized and eager to learn, given my 6 years in project management roles in both agency and corporate settings. In addition, I have 10 years experience as a freelance web and print designer. I'm eager to leverage my experience and new skills as a part of a team or project to build amazing websites and applications.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: APIs, Bootstrap, Express.JS, HTML/CSS, Javascript, JSON, MongoDB, MySQL, NoSQL, Python, React, Sequelize.js

Applications: Adobe Al/PS/ID/Acrobat, Basecamp, BLUE, Esko, Filemaker Pro, Google Apps, Heroku, Office365, Repl.it, VS Code,

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer/Web Designer Freelance

2011-2021

Toronto, ON

Creating brands for people and businesses including services such as brand development, print design, ebook design, web design, and social media management.

Assistant Packaging Manager, PLM UX Team Loblaw Brands, Loblaw Companies Limited

2019-2020 Toronto, ON

Coordinating user experience sessions with internal and external users (both in person and via Webex) for development of new Project Lifecycle Management (PLM) system for Loblaw Brands. Also working on user acceptance testing managed with JIRA (responsible for testing and updating tickets), and managing development of packaging portal, providing documentation and testing to ensure requirements have been met. *Kev Accomplishments:*

- 100% completion of user experience sessions
- Praised for positive attitude, organization skills and packaging expertise
- Presented project update and Loblaw Brands Operations quarterly meeting

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Assistant Packaging Manager, Technical Packaging Loblaw Brands, Loblaw Companies Limited ON

2017-2019 Toronto, Supporting our brands by managing and growing the Loblaw Brand Printer Program, collecting and analyzing packaging and sustainability data, and supporting the product teams and business units with their packaging and printer related needs.

Client Coordinator 2014-2017 Schawk!, SGK Toronto,

ON

Managing packaging and marketing projects for CPG customers, including developing timelines, working with internal teams on creative and concept briefs, and coordinating the approval process.

Project Coordinator & Administrative Assistant Jar Creative

2013

Toronto,

ON

Managing multiple concurrent web and print projects including the creation and execution of project work plans and revising as appropriate to meet changing needs and requirements.

PROJECTS

Get Growing | Github: https://github.com/ryanbrowne360/GardenAppProject | Deployed: https://murmuring-dawn-18632.herokuapp.com/

- Get Growing is an online platform that can be used to track your garden. It allows you, the mighty home gardener, to create a new post for every plant in your garden, make field notes and track your progress.
- My core responsibilities included project management, design & front-end development
- Tools/Languages: HTML5, CSS, React, React-Bootstrap, Bootstrap, Adobe Fonts, Font Awesome, Mongoose, Node.js, Express, Heroku & Github Projects

Flame Game | Github: https://github.com/SSamoridny/Project-2-Flame-Game | Deployed: https://tranquil-temple-78360.herokuapp.com/

- Flame Game (an Apothecary of Hilarity), is an ecommerce website that includes a product page, cart and checkout.
- My core responsibilities included design & front-end development
- Tools/Languages: HTML5, CSS, Javascript Bootstrap, Adobe Fonts, Express, Heroku & MySQL

What's for Dinner? | Github: https://github.com/ryanbrowne360/Project1 | Deployed: https://ryanbrowne360.github.io/Project1/

- What's for Dinner? is a web application that helps answer one of life's most important questions. It is a recipe and restaurant finder that uses two different APIs.
- My core responsibilities included design & front-end development
- Tools/Languages: HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap & APIs (Edamam and Yelp)

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp Certificate: University of Toronto, ON

Python 101: Hackbright Academy, Online

Bachelor of Technology, Graphic Communications Management: Ryerson University, Toronto, ON